You are who you ride with.
Concrete Cowboy is a drama, western film directed by Ricky Staub.
Sent to live with his estranged father for the summer, a rebellious teen finds
kinship in a tight-knit Philadelphia community of Black cowboys.
Cole, played by Caleb McLaughlin.
Harp, played by Idris Elba.
Smush, played by Jharrel Jerome.
Rome, played by Byron Bowers.
Nessi, played by Lorraine Toussaint.
Leroy, played by Method Man.
Concrete Cowboy is a 2020 American drama film directed by Ricky
Staub from a screenplay by Staub and Dan Walser.
Based on the novel Ghetto Cowboy by Greg Neri, it was inspired by the real urban African-American
horseriding culture of Philadelphia, specifically, the Fletcher Street Urban Riding Club.
It stars Idris Elba, Caleb McLaughlin, Jharrel Jerome, Byron Bowers,
Lorraine Toussaint, and Clifford "Method Man" Smith.
While the film is completely fictional, several real members of the Fletcher Street riding community
play supporting characters who give voice to real issues that the community faces.
Concrete Cowboy had its world premiere at the Toronto International Film Festival on
September 14, 2020, and was digitally released on Netflix on April 2, 2021.
The tone is emotional.